{
    "subject": "resource/Barbara_Loden",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Barbara Loden (July 8, 1932 \u2013 September 5, 1980) was a Broadway Tony award-winning American stage and film actress, model, and stage/film director. She was the first woman to write, direct and star in her own feature film, Wanda, which won the International Critics Award at the 1970 Venice Film Festival.",
    "human_readable": "The comment about Barbara Loden is that she was a Broadway Tony award-winning American stage and film actress, model, and stage/film director who wrote, directed and starred in her own feature film Wanda which won the International Critics Award at the 1970 Venice Film Festival.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9109873175621033,
            "question": "What award did Barbara Loden's film 'Wanda' win at the Venice Film Festival?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9001294374465942,
            "question": "Was Barbara Loden American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8857609629631042,
            "question": "Where did Barbara Loden win a Tony Award?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8725029230117798,
            "question": "What year was Barbara Loden's film 'Wanda' awarded at the Venice Film Festival?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7878373861312866,
            "question": "What awards did Barbara Loden win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.781021773815155,
            "question": "What film did Barbara Loden write, direct, and star in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7580586671829224,
            "question": "Name one achievement associated with Barbara Loden."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7359672784805298,
            "question": "What type of performances was Barbara Loden known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7166805863380432,
            "question": "What was Barbara Loden's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6140689253807068,
            "question": "Besides acting, what other roles did Barbara Loden have in the film industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about Barbara Loden is that she was a Broadway Tony award-winning American stage and film actress, model, and stage/film director who wrote, directed and starred in her own feature film Wanda which won the International Critics Award at the 1970 Venice Film Festival.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2149_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Barbara Loden's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2149_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of performances was Barbara Loden known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2149_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name one achievement associated with Barbara Loden.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2149_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2149_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2149_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2149_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2149_151.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2149_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2149_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2149_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2149_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2149_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2149_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention Barbara Loden as a Broadway Tony award-winning American stage and film actress, model, and stage/film director who wrote, directed, and starred in her own feature film Wanda, which won the International Critics Award at the 1970 Venice Film Festival. This information supports the triple that she was an author of a literary work (Wanda) that received a notable award (International Critics Award)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe provided context confirms that Barbara Loden was a Broadway Tony award-winning American stage and film actress, model, and stage/film director. It also states that she wrote, directed, and starred in her own feature film Wanda, which won the International Critics Award at the 1970 Venice Film Festival."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}